RG 062:168, Town of Woodbury
Connecticut State Library
Town of Woodbury records
circa 1820-1896
Connecticut State Library
Woodbury (Conn.)
10.5 cubic feet
Administratvie, election, court, land, school and tax records for the town of Woodbury.
RG062_168
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Woodbury was named in May 1673.
Scope and Content
Administratvie, election, court, land, school and tax records for the town of Woodbury.
Index Terms
Alternate Creators:
Connecticut. Justice of the Peace (Woodbury)
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Woodbury -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Woodbury -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Woodbury -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Woodbury -- Registers; Scholl enrollment -- Connecticut -- Woodbury -- Statistics; Deeds -- Connecticut -- Woodbury; Justices of the peace -- Connecticut -- Woodbury; Voting registers -- Connecticut -- Woodbury
Places:
Woodbury (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, circa 1820-1896
  - T000599
    - Tax lists, 1850-1851, 1853-1857 (Box Box 1)
    - Bills and orders (Box Box 2)
    - Bills and orders, 1865-1888 (Box Box 3)
    - Bills and orders, 1889-1894 (Box Box 4)
    - Bills and orders, 1895-1896 (Box Box 5)
    - Town meeting records (Box Box 6)
    - Election reports, electors' certificates, and voter registers (Box Boxes 7-9)
    - Deeds (Box Box 10)
    - Justice files (Box Box 10)
    - Tax abstracts, 1841, 1855 (Box Box 11)
    - Fire district individual tax list, 1896 (Box Box 11)
    - Treasurer's books, 1863-1878 (Box Box 12)
    - Abstracts, circa 1841-1878 (Box Box 12)
    - District 8 school register (Box Box 12)
    - Town papers, circa 1820-1880 (Box Box 13)
  - 1994-026
    - Tax calculation records, undated (Box Box 1)